exness.com 2010-12-30

# EXNESS - Privacy policy

Protecting the privacy, personal and financial information of its clients is a priority at EXNESS (hereinafter the "Company"). This Privacy Policy interprets how the Company keeps its Client's information secure. 

### Collection of Personal Information

The Company shall request information from the Client which is necessary for the Client to open personal account. Providing such information is a necessary condition which allows the Company to protect the Client's interests and the Client to execute transactions using personal account without being concerned about the asset security. The Company shall be entitled to collect information which may contribute to improving its understanding of the Client's needs and preferences. 

All information necessary for communication between the Client and the Company is collected directly from clients. 

### Use of Personal Information

The Company uses clients' personal information for the purpose of providing the Client with safe, quality service. 

Personal and contact information received from the Client shall be used to check contact details and verify the Client's identity. The Company shall also use personal information to create accounts, open and modify trading accounts, issue activation codes and access passwords. Client contact information helps the Company improve its services and promptly inform the client about the Company's additional products, opportunities and promotions.

### Branches and Partners 

At the Client's request, the Company may provide information about services offered by the Company's branches and partners. For the purpose of providing more high-quality services, the Company may carry out affiliate relations or conclude marketing agreements with other companies. In order to provide the Client with full, well-timed and qualitative service, the Company may exchange information with its partners and branches. The use of the Client's personal information shall be limited in this case. 

### Disclosure of Client Information to Third Parties

The Company may not disclose Client personal information except in the cases described below. 

The Company shall reserve the right to disclose personal information to a third party if required by law enforcement agencies or other state authorities. The Company shall be entitled to disclose the Client's information as necessary to tax or credit authorities or in the cases when it is necessary for the purpose of protecting the Company's rights and property. 

If a third party receives personal information about a Client, it thereby undertakes to protect such information in a manner similar to the manner described in the Privacy Policy. 

The Company may use a client's personal information only for the purpose of improving the quality of its services.

### Liability Restriction

If the Company's Client decides to use the services of another company and provides this company with his/her/its personal information, the Client should understand that the safety of his/her/its personal data becomes the responsibility of the other company, as well. Before providing another company with personal information, the Client should read its privacy policy. The Company's website is online and may be connected with other websites, so clients must be careful and keep in mind that the Company shall not be responsible for the privacy policies of other websites. 

### Use of Cookies 

In order to ensure the effective operation of the Company's website and Client trading activity, the Company shall use Cookies. Cookies are small text files sent from the Company's web server to the Client's computer. Cookies used by the Company shall not contain any personal data, account numbers or passwords. 

The Company may involve other organizations in administration of website and the collection and analysis of statistical data. Such organizations may establish and use their own Cookies on behalf of the Company, and such Cookies shall not contain personal information. 

### Communication

During registration the Client receives a letter via e-mail which confirms his/her/its registration. The Company may send information about changes and new promotions to its clients via e-mail or receive e-mails with questions and requests from its clients, and such information shall not be deemed confidential. 

By accepting this Privacy Policy, the Client allows the Company to use information received from the Client via e-mail, including various ideas, methods, marketing products and know-how, without any consequent obligations from the Company. An exception shall be the Client's identification data.

The Company shall be entitled to return, save or delete correspondence with the Client at its absolute discretion. 

The Company shall be entitled to follow up on internal messages from clients for the purpose of improving the quality of its services. 

### Changes in the Privacy Policy

Sometimes the Company may update its Privacy Policy. In case substantial changes are made to the Policy, new Privacy Policy shall be published immediately on the Company's website and all clients shall be informed about the changes. The Company recommends that its clients read the Privacy Policy from time to time in order to be aware of the way their information is used. 

The Client may send any questions and suggestions concerning the Privacy Policy to the Company's specialists by e-mailing [legal@exness.com](mailto:legal@exness.com)
